### Coordonnées

www.linkedin.com/in/hang-nguyen-b7183586 (LinkedIn)

### Principales compétences

Adobe Photoshop Figma (Software) Adobe Illustrator

### Certifications

Google UX Design Certificate

Agile Project Management In Baking

# Hang Nguyen

**UI/UX** Designer

Ho Chi Minh-Ville, Viêt Nam

## Résumé

Hello, my name is Hang Nguyen. I'm a graphic designer with 8 years' experience. I decided to challenge myself with a new field which is UI/UX design. So I spent 6 months attending Google's professional UX design course. And now I'm ready to go back to work in a new field.

## Expérience

ACB - Asia Commercial Bank
UI UX Designer
janvier 2022 - Present (3 ans 3 mois)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Apax Leaders
Graphic Designer
janvier 2019 - janvier 2021 (2 ans 1 mois)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

### **Formation**

Architecture University Ho Chi Minh City university bachelor, Industrial art · (septembre 2009 - juin 2013)